ShinY
深影
本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址http://shinybbs.vip
■
最有权势的人也不能凌驾于法律之上
The most powerful are not above the law.
祖国人提供了斯坦·埃德加犯罪的
Homelander has provided evidence of crimes
ShinY
深影
相关证据
committed by Stan Edgar.
维琪 我很高兴你选择了你的同类
Vicky, I'm glad you chose your own kind.
■
ShinY
深影
如果我们要跟他斗
If we need to fight him,
■
翻译：  黑猫 西倜 MiNT Ken 西倜
- 你会帮助我吗 - 好 我加入
- will you help me? - Okay, I'm in.
火车头跟我说了你们的小阴谋
A-Train told me about your little plots.
■
阿莱克斯 天呐
Alex! Oh, my God.
■
校对：  负零     压制： 青鸟
B.C.L.红是什么
What's B.C.L. RED?
杀了士兵男孩的东西
The thing that killed Soldier Boy.
你好呀
Hello, hello.
想必你就是妮娜了
You must be Nina.
我在追查一件特殊的武器
I'm after a particular weapon.
我们有个小活要她去做
We just got to do a little job for her.
ShinY
深影
■
我想试一试
I want to try something.
这不是力量 是惩罚
It's not power. It's punishment.
晚上好 婊子们
Evening, cunts.
你为什么故意对自己做出这种事
Why did you do this to yourself on purpose?
你明明能做得更好 孩子
You're better than this, kid.
ShinY
深影
士兵男孩
Soldier Boy.
ShinY
深影
没有我能凝聚的团队了 布彻
Ain't no team for me to hold together no more, Butcher.
- 抬高她的头 弗兰基 - 亲爱的
- Hold her head up, Frenchie. - Mon coeur!
你在录像吗
Are you recording?
嗯
Yes.
如你所知 实验品的皮肤
As you know, the subject's skin has
显示出非同寻常的韧性
demonstrated remarkable durability.
包括内部组织
Which includes internal tissue.
她怎么样了
How is she?
暂时稳定
Stable, for now.
请注意 由于一月二十四号的操作
Please note that, due to the procedure dated January 24,
实验品的辐射水平仍然很高
the subject still registers high radiation levels.
那个杂种怎么还活着
How the fuck's that cunt still breathing?
二十西弗的辐射
Twenty sieverts of radiation.
硫酸化合物的摄入
Sulfuric acid cocktails.
他都快成为一个行走的切尔诺贝利了
More or less shoved Chernobyl right up his arse.
我们现在将验证他的角膜是否有着
We will now determine whether his cornea
相似的强度
shares a similar strength.
我打赌这就是他获得令人讨厌的新能力的方法
I'll wager that's how he got them nasty new powers.
听着 伙计 我们不能留在这里
Listen, mate, we can't hang about here
去找他 对吧
looking for him, right?
他现在是俄罗斯人的麻烦了
He's Ivan's problem now.
我们得把山崎纪带回家 给她找个合适的医生
We got to get Kimiko home to a proper doctor.
你根本不在乎山崎纪
You don't give a shit about Kimiko.
也不在乎任何人
Or anyone else.
让这事翻篇吧 伙计
Oh, come off it, mate.
听着 我当时吃了药
Look, I took a fucking drug.
你别忘了 我刚刚救了你的命
And in case you forgot, I just saved your life.
你杀了火药 对吧
You killed Gunpowder, didn't you?
是用你的那双激光眼吗
Did you use your little laser eyes?
你说的太他妈对了 我是这么做了
You're too fucking right, I did.
而且感觉很好
And it felt good.
终于 我能跟他们处在同一级别了
For once, I leveled the fucking playing field.
布彻
Butcher,
我们所做的关键是
the whole point of what we do,
整件事他妈的关键点是
the whole goddamn point,
没人应该拥有那种能力
is that no one should have that kind of power.
那不就是歌舞升平的童话世界了吗
Well, ain't that just fucking fairies and dancing dildos, eh?
我正好住在这里 伙计
I happen to live right down here, mate,
在地球上
on planet Earth.
操
Oh, fuck.
看着就像青蛙克米特射了你一嘴
Looks like Kermit the Frog had a right wank in your mouth.
我没事 我很好 好吗
No, I'm good, okay?
我看出来了
So I see.
怎么了
What?
没事
Nothing.
我知道现在是困难时期
I know these are difficult times,
但怀着最大的谦逊 我接受沃特国际公司
but with the greatest humility, I accept your nomination as CEO
首席执行官的提名
of Vought International.
我十七岁时 我母亲因癌症去世前
You know, my mother used to say, before she
她曾说过
died of cancer when I was 17...
好了 艾希莉 够了 别尬聊了
Okay, Ashley, that's enough. Let's not bring the room down.
不好意思 先生 当然了
Apologies, sir. Of course.
大家好 不好意思我来迟了
Hello, everyone. Sorry I'm late.
谢谢你们上到九十九层来
Thank you so much for coming up to 99,
免礼 平身
the mountain to Muhammad, as it were.
好了
Okay.
鉴于这是我第一次参加董事会
Seeing as it's, uh, my very first board meeting,
我觉得我们可以轮流
I thought perhaps we'd start by, uh, going around the room
给你们一个
and giving you all a chance
- 自我介绍的机会 - 我是比尔·马什
- to introduce yourselves. - Bill Marsh.
我首先要感谢你 祖国人
And I, for one, would like to thank you, Homelander,
在沃特历史上如此关键的时刻
for giving me the opportunity to serve this board
给我机会为这个董事会服务
at such a pivotal moment in, uh, Vought's history.
我是帕特·威利斯 先生
Pat Willis, sir.
你帮我们摆脱了斯坦·埃德加 恢复了公司的
You've rid us of Stan Edgar and restored honesty, integrity
诚信 正直和创新
and innovation to this corporation.
有个问题 鉴于这里的变动
One question. With the changes around here,
我们的息税折旧摊销前利润将会略有下降
our EBITDA margins will drop a tiny bit.
您打算如何在收益报告上处理这一点
How do you want to handle that on the earnings call?
你叫什么
What's your name?
莫琳
Maureen.
有些话你不吐不快是吧 莫琳
Is there something you want to get off your chest, Maureen?
抱歉 先生
Sorry, sir? Wh...
你觉得你比我更懂行是吗
Do you think you know better than me?
也许你应该
I don't know. Maybe you think you should be
坐在我的位置上
sitting in my chair and...
我应该一路降级 然后坐在你的位置上
I should be sitting all the way down there in yours.
哦 不 先生
No, God, no, sir.
我很抱歉 我只是
I... I'm sorry. I... I was just...
是我太蠢了
It was stupid of me.
我太蠢了 您这么优秀
I'm so stupid, and you're so great.
还有
And... uh...
莫琳 你在让你自己难堪 你应该离开了
Maureen, you're embarrassing yourself. You should go.
所以下一个是谁
So who's next?
在您出色而称职的领导下
We look forward to working hand in glove
我们期待与您合作
under your tremendous
先生
and competent leadership, sir.
能够领导犯罪分析部门十三年
It was my honor to lead Crime Analytics
是我的荣幸
for the past 13 years,
但天下没有不散的宴席
but all good things must come to an end,
沃特董事会觉得是时候做出改变了
and the Vought board decided it was time for a change.
所以 允许我向你们介绍新任
So, allow me to introduce you to the new
犯罪分析部门的上司
head of Crime Analytics:
深海
the Deep.
谢谢大家 谢谢大家
Thank you, thank you.
谢谢你的付出 芭布
Thank you for your service, Bar.
让我们为芭布鼓掌
Let's hear it for Bar.
来吧 她做得很好
Come on, she did great.
对于一个没有实践经验的人来说
For someone with no practical experience,
这很棒了
it's amazing.
我一直梦想着
Look, it's always been a big dream of mine
能够打击犯罪
to be able to fight crime
在海洋里 同样也在陆地上
both at sea and on land.
我来此是告诉你们
I'm here to tell you
如果你足够努力
that if you work hard enough,
没有什么成就是你不能达到的
there's nothing you can't achieve.
标签 远大梦想
Hashtag dream big.
很远大
Real big.
因为沃特会确保正确的男人
Because Vought'll make sure the right man...
不好意思 芭芭拉
Er... Sorry, Barbara.
正确的人得到工作
Right person, gets the job.
所以 为了破冰 我们带来了
So, to break the ice, we brought...
- 纸杯蛋糕 - 纸杯蛋糕
- Cupcakes. - Cupcakes.
- 巧克力碎那家的 - 没错
- From Sprinkles. - That's right.
还有一件事
Oh, and one more thing.
每个人都需要参加
Everyone just needs to sign up for, uh,
绩效评估
performance reviews.
只是走个形式 不用担心
Just a formality, nothing to worry about.
你想去当自由职业者吗
Mmm. You thinking of going freelance?
小心她的头 我们走
Watch her head. Let's go.
她很快就能下地走路了
She'll be up and about in no time.
我们明早见 好吗
We'll see you in the morning, yeah?
去你的
Fuck you.
嘿
Hey.
你还有我呢
You still got me.
就在他刚入选七人队之时
Tragically relapsed into an opioid addiction,
再次对鸦片类药物上瘾
just as he was slated to join The Seven.
自莱恩·比亚斯以来 尚未有一位公众人物
Not since Len Bias has a public figure
在翻红前夕
been lost to a drug overdose
因吸毒过量丧生
- on the cusp of the next... - Hey.
嗨 过来
Hey. Come here.
来
Come here.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我太他妈的抱歉了
I'm so fucking sorry.
我不应该来这儿 这对你不安全
I shouldn't be here. It's not safe for you.
我不在乎 没事的
I don't care. It's okay.
休伊 祖国人杀了阿莱克斯
Hughie, Homelander killed Alex.
他他妈的谋杀了他 这都是我的错
He fucking murdered him, and it's all my fault.
嘿 这不是你的错
Hey. It is not your fault.
过来 来
Come here, come here, come here.
我们有查尔斯顿口香糖
We got Charleston Chew.
有杏仁巧克力味
We got Almond Joy.
蜂蜜坚果味
Bit-O-Honey.
冰箱里还有白爪
There's White Claws in the fridge.
浴缸里有恶心的薰衣草沐浴球
Some of that gross lavender bath bomb shit in the tub.
听着 我知道这些不会让这件事
Look, I know this doesn't make this
好转 但我只是
any better, but I just...
让我也能照顾你一下
Let me take care of you for a second.
告诉我你们找到了那个武器
Tell me you found it.
莫斯科是条死胡同
Moscow was a dead end.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
没有武器 枪 什么都没有吗
No weapon or gun or anything?
操
Fuck.
那是什么杀了士兵男孩
Then what killed Soldier Boy?
你知道吗 我给你拿一瓶白爪好了
Let... You know what? I'm gonna get you a White Claw.
休伊
Uh, Hughie?
你胳膊骨折了
Your arm is broken.
你的护具呢
Where the hell is your cast?
你真的需要一瓶白爪了
You're... you're really gonna want a White Claw.
好吧
Wow. All right.
还要再来一瓶
Gonna have another one.
我只是试着
Um... Just... I'm just trying
弄清楚让你最不高兴的部分是什么
to get a bead on what, uh, part you're most upset about.
是士兵男孩在俄罗斯不见了这部分
Is it the part where, uh, Soldier Boy's loose in Russia,
还是我服用了一些临时化合物V这部分
or the part where I... I took some temporary Compound V?
可能两者都有
it could be both parts. Uh...
- 所有部分 - 但我立马就跟你说了
- All the parts. - I told you right away, though, right?
没有隐瞒
That's... that's... No secrets.
这能挽回一些分数吧
That's got to be worth some points.
你想靠着不对我撒谎挽回一些
You want points for not lying to me?
我想撤回刚刚那句话
I... would like to retract that statement. Um...
休伊 你注射了一种未经沃特
Hughie, you shot up an untested drug
测试的药物
from Vought.
你可能会杀了你自己
You could've gotten yourself killed.
我们已经没有了
We don't have any more.
即使有 我也不会再注射了
And even if we did, I... I wouldn't take it.
感觉太糟了
It was awful.
就像宿醉
Like, uh, the hangover, all of it, just...
非常讨厌那种感觉
absolutely hated it.
- 你明明很喜欢 - 我太他妈喜欢了
- You loved it. - I fucking really loved it.
这太酷了 你知道我的
It was awesome. I mean, you know me.
如果在以前 我旁边车上的人瞪我
If a guy in the car next to me gives me a dirty look,
我肯定会以速激里唐老大开车一样的速度
I'm like fucking Dom Torreto taking off,
飞快逃开
trying to get away from him 'cause I'm quick
因为我最看重家人
and I'm all about family.
但在俄罗斯时
But in Russia...
我根本没有害怕
I wasn't scared.
我救下了马文
I-I... I saved M.M.
我
Me.
我可以 瞬移
I could, like, teleport.
- 瞬移 - 是的 我就
- Teleport? - Yeah, I... I just...
我知道我该怎么做
I knew how to do it.
我只要绷紧臀部 然后起跳
I just clenched my butt, and-and I jumped, and...
不 休伊 那是非常愚蠢而且危险的行为
No. Hughie, that was stupid and dangerous.
我也不能没有你
I can't lose you, too.
天哪 抱歉 抱歉 你说得对
Oh, God, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You're right.
到此为止了
It's over.
那么
So...
我们现在干什么呢
what do we do now?
我不知道
I don't know.
但不管怎样 我们都会一起解决
But whatever it is, we'll figure it out together.
你和我一起对抗世界
You and me against the world, right?
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
士兵男孩他妈的怎么可能还活着
How the fuck is Soldier Boy still alive?
多亏了我们 世界上又多出来一个疯子
Another nutter loose in the world, thanks to us.
你看起来简直像坨加热过的屎
You look like warmed-over shit.
至少到了早上我就会是清醒的了
Well... least I'll be sober in the morning.
你依然会是一名超人类
You'll still be a Supe.
要是超人类都如此卑鄙
Well, if Supes are so fucking vile,
你为什么还想成为超人类呢
why do you want to be one again?
那些药你打算怎么办
What are you gonna do with those?
谢了 我不喝
No, thanks.
我已经戒了好几个月了 混蛋
I've been sober four months, asshole.
我戒了一年了
It's been a year for me.
利用祖国人的儿子怎么样
What about Homelander's son?
不行
No.
瑞恩还要好几年才能对抗他
Be years before Ryan can take him on.
那飞机上的视频呢
What about that plane video?
我知道这对你而言可能不是特别明智
I mean, I know it wouldn't be so brilliant for you,
但
but...
至少能揭开他的真面目
least it'll pull back the curtain on the cunt.
会把他逼上绝路的
Would send him over the edge.
他很可能会杀害数百万人
He'd end up killing a million people.
视频也只能吓唬吓唬他
The video was always a bluff.
对我来说不是的
Not to me it ain't.
我以为我恨他
I thought I hated the guy.
我嗑过很多东西
I done them all.
可卡因 病毒 海洛因
Coke, E, meth, smack.
没有一样能跟这个比
Ain't nothing like this.
以前击败一个超人类要花费几个月
Used to be months of leg work to take down a Supe.
而火药
Gunpowder...
甚至不需要一秒钟
not even a New York minute.
一定感觉很棒吧
Must've felt good.
我讨厌注射后的每一秒
I hated every second.
不
No.
V让我变得更加
The V just made me more...
像我自己
... me.
获得强大力量的同时
With great power comes the absolute certainty
你就会暴露本性
that you'll turn into a right cunt.
人就是这样 对吗
I mean, that's the thing, right?
你们都是人类
You're all just people.
V只不过
All the V does is just
把内心深处的东西放大了而已
amp up all that shit that's already inside.
你们这些人 不过是行走的核装置罢了
Your lot? Just a bunch of walking nuclear erections.
你知道吗 不仅仅是祖国人
You know? A-and it's not just Homelander.
你们所有人都应该消失
I mean, you-you fucking all got to go.
你们中的
Every fucking last...
每一个
... one of you.
是的
Yeah.
怎么 你还是觉得我配不上你吗
What? You still think you're too good for me?
巧克力酸橙
Chocolate limes.
给她醒了吃的
For when she wakes up.
我祈祷她渡过难关
I pray she pulls through.
十名俄罗斯士兵死亡
Ten dead Russian soldiers.
一座机密的实验室被摧毁
A classified lab destroyed.
我在克里姆林宫的三位线人
Three of my contacts in the Kremlin
失踪了
have disappeared already.
塞尔盖 有一条颠覆不破的自然法则
You know, Sergei, there is this absolute natural law.
是这么说的
That law, it says
你不能搞我 只能我搞你
you do not fuck me, I fuck you.
来找你的是布彻先生
It was Monsieur Charcutier who came to you,
和你交易的也是他 去找他解决啊
made the deal with you. Take it up with him.
我不认识他 我只认识你
I don't know him. I know you.
你是介绍我们的中间人
You're the one who introduced us.
该由你来偿还债务
You're the one who pays the debt.
你现在为我工作
You work for me now.
绝不可能
Absolument pas.
在你离开我投奔布彻之前
You know, before you abandoned me for Butcher,
你经常拧自己的手
you always wrung your hands.
哦 妮娜 我不能杀人
"Oh, Nina, I cannot kill.
我心里难受
It's like acid to my heart."
但你总杀人
Yet you always did.
彼得·西蒙诺夫和他的女儿卡特琳娜
Pyotr Semenov and his daughter Katarina.
你今天给我解决掉
You do it today.
她只是个孩子
She's just a child.
从前这对你来说可不是问题
That's never stopped you before.
解决完给我打电话
Call me when it's done.
山崎
Mon cour?
山崎 嘿
Mon cour? Hey.
你醒啦
Ca va?
你感觉怎么样
How are you feeling?
是士兵男孩干的
It was Soldier Boy.
你为什么在笑
Why are you smiling?
- 我没有自己治愈 - 嗯
- I didn't heal! - Hmm.
给我一个重一点的东西
Hand me something heavy!
重一点
Something heavy!
太重了
It's too heavy!
一定是因为士兵男孩
It must've been Soldier Boy!
我的超能力没有了
My powers are gone!
需要帮忙吗
Can I help you?
超音速如此信任你 你却害死了他
Supersonic trusted you, and you got him killed.
- 我不知道你在说什么 - 你个懦夫
- I don't know what you're talking about. - You fucking coward.
你怎么就这么渴望和你恨的人待在一起
Why are you so desperate to be with people who hate you?
林赛·格雷厄姆送来祝贺
Congrats from Lindsey Graham.
他可真是个舔狗
He's such a gooch-licker.
不管怎么样 我希望你能知道祖国人
Anyway, I hope you know how much Homelander
会对你的忠诚感激不尽
appreciates your loyalty.
他比过去任何时候都更需要可以信任的人
Now more than ever, he needs people he can trust.
感谢你能成为队伍一员
So, to thank you for being a team player,
祖国人同意和你和蓝鹰见一面了
Homelander has agreed to a meeting with you and Blue Hawk.
太好了
Okay, great.
- 多谢 - 好的
- Thanks. - Yeah.
那我出去叫他进来
I'll just pop outside and get him.
什么 现在吗
What? Like, right now?
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hey.
- 感谢你能来得这么快 - 哦
- Thanks for coming on such short notice, Blue Hawk. - Oh.
火车头
A-Train.
嗨
Hey.
忠实粉丝
Big fan.
酷 耶
Cool. Yeah.
- 蓝鹰 - 嗯
- Blue Hawk. - Yeah.
我想和你聊聊你在特伦顿巡逻的事
I wanted to talk to you about your patrols in Trenton.
好像有些过度了
Little excessive.
嗯 谁说的
Hmm? Says who?
很多黑人群众都这说
Well, a lot of Black folks.
没有
No.
不 这跟是不是黑...
No. This has nothing to do with...
美籍非裔完全没有关系
... African Americans.
你和我在学校里都是跟着布林克教练训练的
You and me both trained with Coach Brink at school.
他教我们要完全掌控一切
We were taught to dominate totally.
是的 但是
Yeah, but...
你基本上只在黑人区这么做
you're mostly just doing it in-in Black neighborhoods.
你也不希望别人说你是种族歧视吧
And you don't want people to say that you're being racist, right?
实际上说别人种族歧视的人才是种族歧视
You know, it's actually racist to call somebody racist.
这是什么
What is this?
是开除吗 你们要把我踢出去吗
Is this, like, a "Cancel" Thing? Am I being canceled?
我能做什么来弥补吗
What can I do to make this right?
不用做很多
Wouldn't take much.
我也不知道 道个歉之类的吧
I don't know. Make an apology or some shit.
真是个好主意 谢谢你告诉我
What a great idea. Thank you for saying that.
我敢说祖国人也会很赞同的
I'm sure Homelander would really, really appreciate that,
蓝鹰
Blue Hawk.
嘿 说个时间地点吧
Hey, name the time and place.
这些工作非常重要
It is so important to do the work,
进行一些困难的交流
to have the difficult conversations.
你们太棒了
This is so great, you guys.
怎么回事
What the fuck?
嘿 老兄
Hey, buddy?
你还好吗 兄弟
You okay, buddy?
我和你们其他人不一样
I'm not just like the rest of you.
我更强大 我更聪明
I'm stronger. I'm smarter.
我比你们更优秀
I'm better.
我更优秀
I am better!
我不是什么
I'm not some
软弱无能只会跪着哭的宝宝
weak-kneed fucking cry baby...
- 嘿 看看这是谁 - 托德
- Hey, look who it is. - Todd.
- 嗨 宝贝 - 爸爸
- Hey, baby. - Daddy!
啊 嘿
Ah... hey!
- 你准备好了吗 - 准备好了
- You ready? - Yeah.
好了 去拿上你的背包
All right. Go get your backpack.
她说起去科技中心的事就说个不停
She can't stop talking about this Science Center trip.
我的一生中 人们一直试图控制我
All my life, people have tried to control me.
整整一生
My whole life.
托德 你
Todd, you, uh...
你怎么让珍妮看这个人
you got Janine watching this guy?
我知道 我知道
I know, I know.
他说话可能有些粗鲁 但看这个对珍妮有好处
His language gets a bit salty, but it's good for her.
有什么好处
How is this good for Janine?
呃 因为他是美国最伟大的英雄
Um, because he's America's
他拯救了上千人
greatest hero who saves thousands of people.
他挺身而出打击罪犯
He's standing up to the crooks,
打击当局和传统媒体
the corporations and the legacy media.
你加一下我的脸书好友
Hey, you friend me on Facebook,
我给你发点东西
I'll send you some stuff that will...
托德 我不想让珍妮再看到
Todd, I don't want Janine watching
任何一点关于这个垃圾的内容
any more of this garbage.
- 你明白了吗 - 我准备好了
- Do you understand? - Ready.
为什么 珍妮很喜欢祖国人 他是她的偶像
Why? Janine loves Homelander. He's her favorite.
真的吗 宝贝
Isn't that right, sweetie?
因为祖国人就是个疯子
'Cause Homelander is a psycho
- 他就是坨屎 就是这样 - 爸爸
- piece of shit, that's why. - Daddy.
你要在孩子面前这样吗 马文
You want to pull it back in front of the kid there, Marvin?
她不是其他孩子 她是我女儿
It's not the kid. She's my daughter.
- 好吧 - 为您带来本时段的最新新闻
- Okay. - We have breaking news this hour.
曼哈顿中城刚刚发生爆炸
An explosion just rocked midtown Manhattan.
早些时候的报道表示有十九人遇难
Early reports indicate 19 are dead.
纽约警察局和超人类事务局
The NYPD and Bureau of Superhuman Affairs...
宝贝 我很抱歉 但是爸爸得离开一下
Baby, I'm sorry, but Daddy's got to go.
爸爸 不要 我想去科学中心
No. Daddy, I want to go to the Science Center.
你这是干嘛 她都想了一个礼拜了
What are you doing? She's been waiting for this all week.
我做错什么了吗
Did I do something wrong?
宝贝 你没有
No, baby.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
纽约警察局和超人类事务局
The NYPD and Bureau of Superhuman Affairs
声称这是一个未知超级反派所为
are calling it the work of an unknown supervillain.
而此刻 我们还在等待
At this time, we're still waiting
来自官方的更多消息
for more information from authorities...
祖国人 你在听我说话吗
Homelander? Did you hear me?
抱歉 你说什么
Sorry, what?
我是说 我们应该出面处理 立刻
I said we need to handle this. Now.
被证实死亡 并有数十人受伤
... confirmed killed, with dozens more injured.
是的 我们当然应该处理
Uh, yeah, of course we do. Okay.
那么 定下周日所有节目的档期
So, book slots on all the Sunday shows.
告诉民众 没什么可担心的
Tell them that, uh, there's nothing to worry about,
完全没有
not a thing.
一切都在我们的控制之中
We got everything under control.
- 好主意 - 非常的好
- That's smart. - So smart.
- 那我们就 - 老天啊 我的意思是
- So we're gonna... - Jesus, I meant that
我们必须立刻阻止那个人
we need to stop this guy!
你能注意一下自己的语气吗 亲爱的
Could you watch your fucking tone, please, darling.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我只是 我是说
I just, I mean...
你觉不觉得
Don't you think that
可能最好的处理方法就是找到他
maybe the best way to handle this is to find him?
我怎么没想到 这不明摆着吗
I never thought of that. Obviously.
天呐 那你还不快点去做
God. O-okay, so why don't you go and do that?
以一己之力拯救世界
Hmm? Run along and save the day.
与此同时 大人们
Meanwhile, the grown-ups,
则需要担心股价
well, we got to worry about the share price
还有税息折旧摊销前利润率  明白吗
and the EBITDA margins, okay?
- 非常 - 感谢
- Thank you. - So much.
嘿 是我
Hey. It's me.
告诉我 这不是我认为的那个人
Tell me this isn't who I think it is.
或许正是你认为的那个人
Probably exactly who you think it is.
噢 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
听着 我们现在到现场了
Look, we're coming up on the site now.
你们的犯罪分析科能去找他吗
Can your Crime Analytics people look for him?
我这就去 休伊 你要小心
I'm on it. Just be careful, Hughie.
老天爷啊
Fucking hell.
休伊
Hughie.
艾薇
Ivy.
你好
Hey, uh...
早上好
Morning, morning.
- 维琪也来了吗 - 她在来的路上
- Is Vicky here? - She's on her way.
你不是摔断胳膊了吗
Didn't you break your arm?
是的
Yeah, um...
结果只是严重的扭伤
Yes. It turns out it's a bad sprain,
- 所以我恢复了 回头见 - 好的
- so I... I'm okay. I'll see you later. - Okay.
喂
Oi.
你还认为他是苏联人的麻烦吗
Still think he's the Reds' problem?
好了 放松点 伙计
All right. Easy, mate.
滚开
Fuck you.
我自己会找到他的
I'll find him myself.
找到他之后你能干嘛呢
And what you gonna do when you find him, eh?
小子 你根本不是他的对手
He's well out of your league, son.
你需要帮手
You need help.
你需要我们
You need us.
关于我有多混蛋 我们可以改日再聊
Oh, we can talk about what a cunt I am another time.
但此刻 让我们关注手上的事情
But right now, let's just focus on the job at hand.
让我帮你搞定士兵男孩
Let me help you with Soldier Boy.
之后我们就互不相欠 再无往来
I owe you that much, and then you don't got to see me no more.
以我对你的了解 你应该有线索了
Knowing you, you already got a lead?
那是当然 看看我们在哪
Course I fucking do. Look at where we are.
传奇
The Legend.
我打赌士兵男孩去找过他了
Want to bet Soldier Boy paid him a visit?
- 你要吃另一半吗 - 不要
- Do you want the other half? - No. No.
现在不要 谢谢 你说什么来着
Not right now, thanks. You were saying?
要找到这个人 我们就得梳理
To find the guy, we'd have to comb through
市内的每一台摄像头
every CCTV camera in the city.
这需要十几个分析员两班倒
It would take a dozen analysts working double shifts.
明白 那我们开干吧
Okay, then let's do it.
所有人都去哪里了
Where is everyone?
我们就是所有人
We are everyone.
绝大部分都被深海炒了
Deep fired most of the department.
什么 为什么
What? Why?
他说那些人以前发过些
They had some tweets over the years
批评祖国人的帖子
he said were critical of Homelander.
他说他只要有团队精神的人
Said he only wants "Team players."
我能吃那一半吗
Can I have that half?
多谢
Thank you.
瑞奇
Reg.
伙计 你来这里干嘛
What you doing here, man?
搞什么
What the fuck?
- 他想道个歉 - 他跟你来的吗
- He wants to apologize. - He came with you?
还带了摄制组 不是吧 伙计
And a camera crew? Come on, man.
听着 你得到公开道歉
Listen, you get a public apology,
沃特得到宣传 这是双赢
Vought gets some publicity. It's a win-win.
所以就大摇大摆地来了
You just spring this shit on me?
- 你有毛病吗 - 这不是你想要的吗
- What's wrong with you? - Isn't this what you wanted?
让我用自己的平台来帮助社区 不是吗
For me to use my platform to help the community, right?
就五分钟
Five minutes.
好的
All right.
不好意思
Sorry, sorry.
是我头盔里的金属造成的
It's the metal in my helmet.
好了
All right.
致特伦顿的居民
To, uh, the residents of Trenton,
感谢你们今天给我这个机会
thank you for giving me the opportunity
说几句话
to speak with you today.
众所周知 超级英雄们
As you know, superheroes often have to make,
在打击犯罪时 经常必须在
like, uh, split-second decisions
瞬间作出决定 而我对于自己
when fighting crime, a... a... and I apologize
任何可能被视为
if any of mine have been...
种族歧视的行为而道歉
perceived as being... racist.
但我不是那样的人
But that is not who I am, okay?
只要去问问我的朋友
Just ask my friends,
他们很多都是黑人
many of whom are, uh, are Black,
譬如火车头
like A-Train.
我不看肤色
I do not see color.
我只看谁犯罪
I only see crime.
作为对你们所有人的承诺 我会向
And as a sign of my commitment to you all, I am donating
本社区中心捐赠一万美元 谢谢
$10,000 to this community center. Thank you.
你对雷蒙德·塔克做的事怎么算
What about what you did to Raymond Tucker?
这个嘛 他是个罪犯
Well, he-he-he was a criminal.
他手无寸铁
He was unarmed.
你会对一个在米尔山的白人
Would you have done the same thing
做出同样的事情吗
to a white guy in Mill Hill?
犯罪在哪 我就在哪
I-I go where the crime is,
而犯罪正好就发生在黑人社区
and the crime just happens to be I-in Black neighborhoods.
这不是我的错
That-That's not my fault.
好了 好了 到此为止
All right, all right. No, that's enough here.
结束了 你道了歉
We're done here. Just say you're sorry,
我们可以走了
and we can get out of here. Yeah.
你们去了解一下
You know what? Do your research.
黑人犯下
Like, Blacks commit
谋杀案的比例高得出奇
a disproportionate number of murders.
那你谋杀的所有黑人呢
How about all the Black men you murdered?
那你告诉我他们为什么那么有攻击性
How about you tell me why were they so fucking aggressive?!
我是在正当防卫
I was acting in self-defense.
你有超能力 他们没有
You got powers! They don't!
- 黑人命也是命 - 给我滚 蓝鹰
- Black lives matter! - Fuck you, Blue Hawk!
闪人 闪人
Walk away, walk away.
你干嘛 快离开
Where you going? Get the fuck out.
- 快点 离开 - 所有命都是命
- Come on, out! - All lives matter.
- 所有命都是命 - 黑人命也是命 混蛋
- All lives matter. - Black lives matter, motherfucker!
超英命也是命 超英命也是命
Supe lives matter. Supe lives matter!
超英命也是命 你们这些忘恩负义的家伙
Supe lives matter, you fucking ingrates!
嘿 蓝鹰
Hey, Blue Hawk!
给我闭嘴
Shut the fuck up!
给我滚开
Fuck out of here!
- 糟糕 - 蠢货们
- Shit! - Stupid fucks!
闭嘴 给我滚开
Shut the f... Get the fuck out of here!
停手
Stop!
噢 天呐
Oh, my God!
为什么
Why?!
内特
Nate?
Nate!
就放门口
Just leave it.
什么
What?
把该死的蛤蜊拼盘放门口就好
Leave the goddamn clams casino at the door.
混蛋 我不是送外卖的 开门
This ain't Grubhub, motherfucker. Open up.
马文 嘿
Marvin. Hey.
这个垃圾还是跟着你不放吗
I see you still got this piece of dog shit stuck to your boot.
给我滚开 你这个老不死的
Oh, go do one, you withered old cunt.
这是休伊
This is Hughie.
休伊 你知道他是谁吗
Hughie, you know who this is?
他不知道我是谁 多读点书 小子
He doesn't know who I am? Read a fucking book, kid.
这位就是 传奇
This... this is The Legend.
这个绰号真厉害
That's, uh, quite a nickname.
这可不是个绰号 这是个段位
No, it's not a name. It's a level.
传奇 我们需要谈谈
Legend, we need to talk.
- 他不行 - 他会守规矩的
- Not him. - He'll behave.
我保证
You got my word.
这事很重要 你欠我的
This is important, and you owe me.
这是你和罗伊·谢德吗
Is that you and Roy Scheider?
这是《霹雳钻》首映式后
That's at the Chateau
在庄园酒店拍的
after the Marathon Man premiere.
罗伊·谢德 达斯汀 安杰丽卡 阿帕奇大酋长
Roy Scheider, Dustin, Anjelica, Big Chief Apache.
那一晚我有点迷迷糊糊的
That whole night's a little cloudy to me.
但你如果去问阿米·阿徹德
But if you ask Army Archerd,
他会说 我和黄金艺妓打得火热
I was balls deep in Golden Geisha,
而似乎马龙·白兰度则和我打得火热
and Marlon Brando was apparently balls deep in me.
怎么了
What?
这现在算同性恋了 滚吧 管他呢
That's gay now? Fuck you. Who cares?
有什么区别
What's the difference?
不管怎样 在那之后 我让马龙
Anyway, after that, I got Marlon to cut his quote
在《钢铁骑士》中自降片酬 那么我问你们
on that Steel Knight picture, so I ask you,
谁占了谁的便宜
who fucked who?
他来过这里 是吗
He was here, wasn't he?
不用了 我饱了 可卡因吃饱了
Oh, no, I'm-I'm good. I'm-I'm full. Of cocaine.
好吧
All right.
现在的沃特只注重欢迎度
See, now Vought is all demo points
和观众调查
and audience testing,
多亏了那些背后捅刀子的杂种
thanks to those backstabbing fucks
埃德加和史迪威
Edgar and Stillwell.
是的 我知道她死了
And yes, I know she's dead.
- 还是要叫她去死 - 在史迪威之前
- Fuck her anyway. - So, The Legend was
传奇是沃特英雄管理
the VP of Hero Management over at Vought
部门的副主席
before Stillwell came in.
他会时不时地帮助我们
He helps us out from time to time.
他真的不知道我是谁
He really doesn't know who I am?
当我掌权的时候 一切都靠本能
See, when I was in charge, you go with your gut.
那时候的英雄才是英雄
That's when heroes were heroes,
而不是这些提线木偶
not these stage-managed silicone dolls.
我甚至都没有看到祖国人出过汗
I've never even seen Homelander sweat,
更别说在比佛利山的酒店里和
let alone butter churn half the cast of Falcon Crest
《鹰冠庄园》一半的演员云雨 而我做到了
at the Beverly Hills Hotel, which I did.
两个词
Two words.
香农·特威德
Shannon Tweed.
传奇
Legend.
士兵男孩来找过你
Soldier Boy came to see you.
我要知道他说了什么
I need to know what he said.
你怎么了 疯了吗
What are you, crazy?
马文 他早就挂了
Marvin, he's a fucking doornail.
那么那些可卡因是给谁的
So who's that coke for?
是给我的
That's just me.
我正在写回忆录
I'm writing my memoir.
这本书将会一鸣惊人
It's gonna be really dynamite.
所以我
So I'm, you know,
我写书 吸毒两开花 我发誓
I'm burning the candle at both ends. I swear.
以我孩子生命的发誓
I swear on my kids' lives.
你恨你的孩子们
You hate your fucking kids.
如果你碰到他们也会恨他们
So would you if you met them.
如果我对那面镜子进行指纹检测
So, if I ran the prints on that mirror,
能检测出谁的指纹
who would I come up with?
- 什么 - 别担心
- Huh. - Don't worry.
士兵男孩不会追踪到你的 相信我
Soldier Boy's not gonna trace this back to you. Trust me.
相信你
Oh, trust you.
就像我相信他一样
Like I trusted him?
你忘了上次我帮忙的后果吗
You forget what happened last time I helped?
- 未成年妓女电击受伤案吗 - 嗯
- The underage hooker sting on Electroshock? - Oh. Oh.
你不能相信那种人
You can't trust a man like that.
所有与他相关的人和事都会变得糟糕
Everything and everyone he touches turns to shit.
相信我
Well, you can trust me
我会用那条腿打烂你的脑袋
to bash your fucking brains out with that leg, mate.
布彻 拜托
Butcher, please.
我是你可以信任的人
Look, I'm the one you trust.
你知道士兵男孩对我的家人做了什么
Now, you know what Soldier Boy did to my family.
因为是你批准的善后
And you know because you okayed the cover-up.
我做过无数次这样的事了
Shit, I... I okayed a million cover-ups.
每次都是折磨
And they're all tearing you up.
把这件事处理好 行吗
So just make this one right, will you?
我以为我看见鬼了
I thought I was staring at a ghost,
结果是他
but it was him.
他的胡子乱成了一团
He had a fucked-up beard, maybe,
- 但他没变老 - 等等 他不会变老
- but he hadn't aged a day. - Wait, so he doesn't get old?
就像风暴女吗
Like Stormfront?
我们一直保守着这个秘密
We kept that under wraps.
- 尽管他和菲比·凯茨
Though it got a little fishy when he starred
出演爱情与战争时有点可疑
in that Love and War picture with Phoebe Cates.
当时他六十三岁 她十九岁
He was 63. She was 19.
记得偷天陷阱吗
Oh, fuck. Remember Entrapment?
康纳利上了泽塔·琼斯 他比那厉害一千倍
Connery banged Zeta-Jones. He was, like, a thousand.
士兵男孩怎么在这里
Why was Soldier Boy here?
来拿他的超级战衣
Came to pick up his super suit.
我保管着的
I held on to it.
你懂的 我是个感性的人
You know me. I'm sentimental.
尽管我为凯利·勒布罗克
Although I did actually wear the suit once
穿过一次战衣
for Kelly LeBrock.
她也是感性的人
By the way, her, too.
你不认识凯利·勒布罗克 去谷歌上搜一下
You don't know Kelly LeBrock? Fucking google it.
大写L 大写B
Big "L." Big "B."
其它字母小写
The other letters, small.
那他有没有告诉你他接下来要去哪里
So, did he tell you where he was going next?
有没有说会炸掉五十九号路上的一家餐厅
Or that he was gonna blow up a fucking restaurant on 59th?
谁能了解天才的行事风格
Who the hell knows why talent does what they do?
所以这就是天才吧
That's why they're talent.
他还问了他女朋友的地址
He also came for his girlfriend's address.
他要去那里
He's headed there.
绯红伯爵夫人
Crimson Countess?
为什么
Why?
我不认为这会是一场幸福的重聚
I didn't get the feeling it was gonna be a happy reunion,
但我不知道
but I don't know.
或许你们可以过去看看
Maybe you can go there and find out.
但现在赶紧离开这里
But mostly, get the fuck out of here.
今天
Today's attack
- 五十九号路的爆炸 - 是啊
- on 59th Street. - Yeah.
美国到底面临着多大的威胁
How great a threat is America facing?
没有任何威胁
Oh, no threat whatsoever.
确实 把这个人称为
No. Truly, I-it is a stretch
超级反派都有点牵强
to even call this guy a supervillain.
风暴追逐者 风暴女的支持者
The Stormchasers, Stormfront's supporters,
在4chan上说这整件事
said on 4chan that this whole thing
是史丹·埃德加想让你名誉扫地
was an attempt by Stan Edgar to discredit you.
是这样啊
Right. Yeah.
关于风暴追逐者我一无所知
Well, look, I-I don't know anything about Stormchasers,
我能理解他们的想法
but, uh, look, I can understand why they might think that.
我们刚把沃特从腐败和谎言中解放
The minute we free Vought of the corruption
这件事就发生了
and the lies, and this happens.
我觉得时间点过于巧合了
I mean, the timing is, uh, very convenient.
感觉像是高级黑
Smells like a false flag.
这可是你说的 伙计 我可没说
Well, you said it, pal, not me.
你对市长想要在恐怖分子被捕前
And what do you say to the mayor who wants to, uh,
实行宵禁
impose a citywide curfew until the terrorists
- 有何看法 - 拜托
- are captured? - Oh, please.
美国是安全的
America is safe.
很安全
Okay? It is safe.
大家放心外出
So, everyone, get out there.
去想去的餐厅
Go to your restaurants
去看想看的电影
and, uh, go to your movie theaters
过自己想过的日子
and-and live your lives.
开开心心的 好吗
Have fun, okay?
你认为真的是埃德加和市长吗
You think it really was Edgar and the mayor?
也许是杰克·塔珀
Maybe Jake Tapper.
想要搞我
Trying to fuck with me?
让我看起来很可笑吗
Make me look ridiculous?
或许
Or maybe
你只是个偏执恶毒的自恋狂
you're just a paranoid, malignant narcissist
以为地球绕着你转
who thinks everything is about you.
如果他们来真的
Mm, it's not paranoia
就不是妄想症了
if they're really out to get you, though.
而你 梅芙
And you, Maeve.
你要来找我麻烦 对吧
You're out to get me, aren't you?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
威廉·布彻
William Butcher.
你身上到处是他的味道
I can smell him all over you.
你会想方设法地伤害我 不是吗
You really will do anything to hurt me, won't you?
所以
So...
你和威廉在密谋什么
what are you and William cooking up?
也许是你们把那个超级反派带到了小镇
Maybe you two brought that supervillain to town.
约翰
Oh, John.
约翰 拜托
John, come on.
你在说胡话
You're talking crazy.
我没和布彻商量搞事情
I'm not cooking anything up with Butcher.
我们谈谈吧
Let's talk about this.
你怎么敢叫我约翰的
Don't you dare fucking "John" Me.
这次你肯定吃不了兜着走
You're not gonna weasel your way out of this.
你知道这一切里最悲剧的是什么吗
You know the real tragic thing in all of this?
我比任何人都了解你的感受
It's that, more than anyone, I knew what it was like for you.
我们所到之处 人群蜂拥而至
Swarmed everywhere we went.
任何一个小错误都会上头条新闻
Every little mistake, front-page news.
高处不胜寒 是啊 但至少我们有彼此
It is lonely at the top, yes, but at least we had each other.
我们一起面对孤独
We were lonely together.
我曾爱过你
And I loved you.
以我自己的方式
In my own way.
但你
But you...
发生了什么
What happened?
我们之前的一切是真实的吗
Was anything about us ever real?
嗯
Hmm?
刚开始
From the start,
我恨你
I hated you.
而且
But what's more,
我非常可怜你
I fucking pitied you.
你那么的孤苦伶仃
You're completely and utterly alone.
岁月不饶人 你变得愤世嫉俗
You're getting old and bitter.
你可怜我
You pity me?
这就纯属搞笑了
I mean, that's actually kind of funny,
你不觉得吗
don't you think?
那个
Hey.
你想知道其它搞笑的事情吗
You want to know something else that's funny?
弗兰基不接电话
Frenchie's not answering.
山崎纪参加不了
Kimiko's out of commission.
士兵男孩已经占得先机
Soldier Boy's already got a head start.
我们需要后援
We gonna need some backup.
这就是后援
And here it is.
我以为你用完了
I thought you were out.
溜进杜安·里德那里偷了点
Nipped into the Duane Reade, got some more, didn't I?
我知道你对这个垃圾的看法
Look, I know how you feel about this shite,
但对面是士兵男孩
but it's Soldier Boy.
你就不能
So why don't you come down
屈尊一次吗
off your high horse just this once, eh?
- 我爸不会同意的 - 你那个
- My dad wouldn't want it. - Your dad,
死于一场意外
who died of a dodgy ticker,
起诉沃特却一无所获的爸爸会不同意吗
suing Vought and never getting nowhere?
他是这样的
Yeah. Him.
他还说过
You know, he also said,
如果你不明确底线
if you don't draw the line somewhere,
你怎么会知道你的立场
how the hell are you gonna know where you stand?
他们可没什么底线
They ain't drawing no line.
所以我们必须有
Which is why we got to.
我加入 给我一点
I'm in. Give me some.
小子 没听到我刚才说的话吗
Kid, didn't you just hear a goddamn word I said?
你们想要哪个
I mean, who do you guys want? Do you guys w-want
笨拙 软弱 胆小如鼠的休伊
gawky, weak, freaking-the-fuck-out Hughie
还是强壮 自信
or do you want strong, confident,
运筹帷幄的休伊
handling-his-shit Hughie?
有它的话 我就有用武之地了
With it, I can actually help.
没有它的话 我
Without it, I'm...
我就死翘翘了
I-I'm probably dead.
孩子长大了
Lad can think for himself.
- 抱歉 巴雷特女士 - 你到底
- I am so sorry, Ms. Barrett. - What the fuck
- 对梅芙做了什么 - 没事 格雷戈里
- did he do to Maeve? - That's all right, Gregory.
梅芙在马里布的全球健康疗养院
Maeve is at the Global Wellness Retreat in Malibu.
寻求帮助 真的不容易
Asking for help, it's just not easy.
她是真正勇敢的梅芙 不是吗
And she is just truly Brave Maeve, isn't she?
嗯 我现在就想和她谈话
Mm-hmm. I want to speak to her right now.
不幸的是 疗养院不让病人使用
Unfortunately, the facility requires a digital detox
数字通讯设备 但你可以给她留言
for their patients, but I'm sure you can leave her a message.
天呐 艾希莉
Goddamn it, Ashley!
- 我们不能让他这么做 - 你指谁
- We can't let him do this. - Who are you referring to?
他已经失控了
He is out of control.
昨天是超音速
Yesterday, it was Supersonic.
今天是梅芙
Today, it's Maeve.
明天也许轮到你或我了
Tomorrow, maybe it's me or you.
我知道你很害怕
Look, I know you're scared.
我也是 但为了工作搭上性命 不值得
I am, too, but this CEO job, it can't be worth your life.
我没有超能力
I don't have powers.
你不需要有超能力
You don't need powers.
你只需当个人
You just need to be human.
求你了 梅芙在哪
Please. Where is Maeve?
她还活着吗
Is she even alive?
星光 嘘
Look, Starlight, sh...
我是首席执行官
I am CEO.
下次来 记得提前预约
Next time, make a fucking appointment.
他胸部和腰部的脊柱
There's been severe damage
都严重受损
to the thoracic and lumbar regions of the spine.
T6 T7 T8 T9椎体都有撕裂
Lacerations to vertebrae T6, T7, T8 and T9.
内森伤得太重了 以后都无法走路了
The damage is so severe that Nathan will never walk again...
对方想要掏枪
... individual reached for his gun
我必须当机立断 拯救无辜的生命
and I had to act quickly to save innocent lives.
想想我对这个社区的贡献
You know, to think that my donation to this community
竟然还要被一些极左组织的
would be met with such intolerance,
暴徒们如此苛待
you know, by a few Antifa thugs and bad apples,
我真是伤透了心
just breaks my heart.
心寒啊
Just breaks it.
妮娜
我有 声音了
I got... rhythm.
医生 快来
Doctor, come!
她能说话了
She speaks!
我想我得来杯咖啡 你要吗
Oh, I think I need café. You want café?
等等 我马上回来
Well, yeah, I'll be right back.
我已经得到了承诺
I've already got commitments
《小猴当家》里的红毛猩猩
from the orangutan from Dunston Checks In
《极度恐慌》里的僧帽猴 都会参演
and the capuchin from Outbreak.
严格说来 那些都不是黑猩猩
Technically, those aren't chimps.
确实 但它们很有名
No, but they're famous.
会吸引很多人
They're gonna be real draws.
我曾和《极度恐慌》里的猴子合作过
I worked with that Outbreak monkey once.
- 它很棒 - 我跟你说
- He's very good. - I'm telling you,
世界上所有地方中
there is no other place in the world
猴子会最喜欢待在这里
a monkey will want to be than right here.
我很喜欢这样的闲聊
Uh, I love our little chats, you know,
但是 已经开始计时了 所以
but, you know, meter's running, so...
别着急 射很多先生779
Hold your horses, Sir-Cums-A-Lot779.
遵命 伯爵夫人
Yes, Countess.
- 东西你收到了吗 - 当然
- Did you get them? - Sure did.
哇
Wow.
他们比我想象的还要大
Those are much bigger than I thought they would be.
先让这些小家伙们热个身
Let's warm these bad boys up,
然后我会脱掉这身令人发痒的衣服
and I'll get out of this itchy suit.
准备好了
Get ready.
真他妈性感
Fucking sexy.
- 你喜欢吗 - 喜欢
- You like that? - Yeah.
想要吗
You want it?
我准备好了
I'm ready.
把你的胶衣脱掉 把那些东西塞进去吧
Get that spandex down and start popping those things in there.
好
Yeah.
什么鬼
What the fuck?!
哦 不
Oh, no!
什么情况
What the hell?!
你去哪了 我差点就要
Where'd you go? I'm almost...
在吗
Hello?
跟你今晚幻想的轰轰烈烈不一样 是吧
Probably not the dom-sub rumble you fancied tonight, yeah?
这人他妈什么毛病
What the fuck's up with him?
我们不是来伤害你的
We ain't here to hurt you.
但我要告诉你一件事
But I am gonna tell you something,
我不想你吓得尿裤子
and I don't want you to lose your shit.
什么
What?
你的情人正在来这里的路上
Your lover boy's on his way here.
士兵男孩
Soldier Boy.
他还活着
He's alive.
他怎么从俄罗斯逃出来的
How'd he escape from Russia?
有趣了
Well, that's interesting.
你知道他一直在俄罗斯人手上
You knew the Ivans had him all this time?
我必须离开这里
I got to get out of here. Okay.
快给我解开
Untie me right now.
他会杀了我的
He's gonna kill me.
他会把我们都杀了
He's gonna kill all of us.
为什么 你干了什么
Why? What'd you do?
去你妈的
Fuck you, all right?
快放我走 不然我们都得死
Let me go or we're all dead.
你们吵架了
Trouble in paradise, eh?
别担心 亲爱的
Don't you worry, darling.
我们有条大鱼要钓 你就是饵
We got to big fish to hook, and you're the worm.
你在开玩笑吗 开什么玩笑
Is this a joke? Is this a joke?
别这样 放我走吧
Come on. Let me go.
拜托 放我走吧
Come on, guys. Let me go.
求求了 别这样
Come on, guys.
谢谢 给
Thanks. Here.
确定氟烷能起作用吧
We're sure halothane will work?
从俄罗斯人的视频里看来的
Looked that way in the Reds' video.
我们把他放倒 让他失去意识
We knock him out, we keep him out,
然后再考虑怎么处理他
then we figure out what to do with him.
这他妈怎么回事
What the hell's going on?
安妮 你来干什么
Annie, what are you doing here?
马文给我打了电话
M.M. Called me.
- 是吗 - 我就是告诉她
- Did he? - Just told her
我们可能需要一些后援
we might need some backup.
其它没说
That's all.
你不该来这里 好吗 太危险了
Look, y-you shouldn't be here, all right? It's dangerous.
对我来说太危险吗
It's too dangerous for me?
- 那你呢 - 你们两个
- What about you? - Oi, you lot,
要吵去别的地方吵
take your little tiff somewhere else.
我们还有正事要干
We're on the job here.
行吧 来这边吧
Okay, uh, over here. Huh?
我就是不理解你为什么不打电话告诉我
I just don't understand why you wouldn't call me for this.
好了好了 你知道了可能会生气
Okay, okay. Look, you... you're probably gonna be mad...
但既然我答应过不再向你保密 所以
... but I promised no more secrets, right? So...
天哪
Oh, my God.
休伊
Hughie.
等等
Hold... One second.
- 你找到更多的V了 - 只有临时的
- You found more V? - It's temporary V.
都是临时的 好吗 我又不是傻子
It's temporary, okay? I'm not an idiot.
我知道很可疑 我看过《猜火车》
I-I know it's sketchy. I've seen Trainspotting.
但对方是士兵男孩啊
But I-it's Soldier Boy.
我还能做什么呢
I mean, what else was I supposed to do?
- 你还能给我打电话 - 要是你为了救我
- You were supposed to call me. - Yeah, and what if you got hurt
自己受伤了怎么办 安妮
trying to save me, Annie?
我永远都不会原谅自己 但现在你不用救我了
I would never forgive myself. But now you don't have to, okay?
我能保护好自己 甚至我终于可以救你一次了
I can handle myself. I can finally save you for once.
我不需要你来救我 休伊
I don't need you to save me, Hughie.
我需要你这个人
I need you.
你干了什么
What'd you do?
我知道你不会原谅我的
I know you're never gonna forgive me,
但我别无选择
but you left me no choice.
为什么
Why?
马文 我们的事想要成功
I can't draw no line, M.
必须不择一切手段
Not with what I got to do.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你明天早上就没事了
You'll be all right in the morning.
你是实验室里的那个混蛋
You're that asshole from the lab.
没错
That's right.
我就是那个放你出来的混蛋
I'm the arsehole that let you out.
那里就像俄罗斯移动厕所
Russian Porta-Loos, eh?
你想杀了伯爵夫人 是吧
You want the Countess's head on a spike, don't you?
她就在里面 任你处置
Well, she's in there, yours for the taking.
你可以看作是我的诚意
Consider it a gesture of good faith.
什么诚意
Good faith for what?
我在想 我们两个
I was thinking that you and I
可以达成一个小小的约定
could come to a little arrangement.
就是你们说的
What you lot call...
组队
a team up.
本
Ben?
真的是你吗
Is that really you?
你看起很年轻
You look so young.
你老了
You don't.
我真的很抱歉
I'm so, so sorry.
那不是我的主意
It wasn't my idea.
天哪 你得相信我
God, you got to believe me. I-I...
俄罗斯人给了你多少钱
How much did the Russians pay you?
嗯
Hmm?
他们没给
They didn't.
什么
What?
他们什么都没给你吗
They didn't pay you anything?
我爱过你
I loved you.
这么多年来
All those years...
他们用火烧我
... that they burned me
给我注射各种毒药
and that they pumped me full of poison,
我还一直存有希望
I held onto the hope that you would come.
希望你会来救我
That you would save me.
因为我还爱着你
Because I still loved you.
我不爱你
I didn't love you.
我恨你
I hated you.
我们都恨你
We all did.
安妮 拜托 快走吧
Annie, please, just go.
让我们来处理 你可以冲我大喊
Let us handle this. You can yell at me...
发生了什么 他受伤了吗
What happened? Is he hurt?
盯好他
Keep an eye on him.
他服用了大概四五毫克的安眠药
He's had four or five mgs of Rohypnol.
你他妈麻醉了他吗
You fucking roofied him?!
你在干什么
What are you doing?
安妮 听着
Annie, listen.
我们想要一件武器
We wanted a weapon.
士兵男孩就是我们的武器
Soldier Boy's our weapon.
他可以杀死祖国人 也许还有纽曼
He's how we kill Homelander. And Neuman maybe.
如果有人足够强大可以做到 就是他了
If anyone's strong enough, he is.
你早知道布彻会这么做
Y-You knew Butcher was gonna do this?
马文肯定不会同意的 而你
M.M. Never would've gone for it, and you...
- 听着 你不该来这里的 - 哦
- Look, you weren't supposed to be here. - Oh.
还说什么
So...
不再有秘密是吧
no more secrets, huh?
休伊
Hughie...
你这是跟一个杀人凶手合作
you're teaming up with a murderer.
这是我能把你从祖国人手里救下来的唯一方法
This is the only way that I can save you from Homelander.
我是为你才这么做
I'm doing this for you.
不惜一切代价 记得吗
Whatever it takes, remember?
跟我们一起吧
Come with us.
你和我 对抗全世界
You and me against the world.
休伊
Hughie.
求你了 别去
Please don't go.
■
更多精彩 请登录深影论坛 shinybbs.vip
深影字幕组微博 weibo.com/syfansub
■
关注深影字幕组
微信公众号，更
多影视资讯，等
你来发现